Causes of death are many and varied, old age, illness, suicide, but out of that long
morbid list there's one end that people fear above all others, death by fire.
Sunlight. Wait, how long was I out?
Khandro!
You okay? Did you get the infernal? Hey, Benny. Yeah. Barely. You fought so hard you carbonized.
Why, Khandro? If you would let me fight with you, then you wouldn't have had to push yourself so far to defeat that thing.
Why didn't you trust me to help you fight?
Ah, come on, Benny. I took you out of the fight because we can't afford to lose you.
You idiot. The only reason we're all still here is because of you. You're the one that Asakusa needs.
With you hurt like this, who the hell's gonna be-
That'll be your duty now, Benny Maru.
There may be civilians trapped beneath the rubble.
The special fire force.
Of course they'd show up after the fight.
There may still be infernals around as well.
The structures could collapse any minute. Keep your distance!
Hello. I am Sorichiro Aku. Captain of Special Fire Force Company Four.
You're Khandro, yes? I'm told that you're a local leader.
By order of the Emperor, your Hikeshi Fire Brigade is hereby inducted into the Special Fire Force as Company Seven.
Ugh! Screw you! You're just afraid of what we're capable of!
Benny, calm down for a sec. You want us to join you guys? Well, I'd like to hear what we stand to gain from it.
You'd remain an autonomous company, but gain the Empire's support. In addition to new funding, you'd receive equipment, supplies, and skilled soldiers. I don't believe you'll find any reasons to decline this offer.
Sorry, I can't give you an answer immediately. I need time to consider.
It will be quite reassuring to have brave soldiers like you on the Force. I await your favorable response.
You want to become an imperial laugh dog? If we'd had the resources of an official company, we probably could have prevented a lot of damage and saved a lot of lives.
If the Empire wants to exploit us, fine. We can just exploit them right back.
It's my own fault I ended up like this. Waka had no say. He's got no reason to feel guilty.
You put yourself through all that to protect Captain Shimon?
Waka doesn't realize it, but he's a natural leader. I don't regret taking a fall for him then or breaking up your fight today.
As soldiers, you should understand. This life of mine isn't worth much. So if I can help Waka, I'll put it on the line.
You shouldn't do that.
My family, the people I loved most are gone. At this point, I can barely remember them. Life is precious. There's no such thing as a worthless one. At least, not to me.
Your life is worth as much as anyone else's. Please believe that. And before you decide to throw yours away, ask me to help you, and I will come running.
Come running.
Thanks, Shinra. I appreciate your perspective. Until you figure out what means the world to you, I'll take your help.
What means the world?
Glad I got a chance to talk to you. Feeling a lot better now. I can't lie around all day. So I'm gonna ask around too.
I don't suppose we'd be allowed to help out with that.
That's fine by me. As long as I'm there to watch you, it isn't a problem.
There you are, dirtbag!
What the hell's going on out here?
We don't know.
I don't know my God.
Let's get to her.
It's a dream.
It's a time for me to go.
We have any support.
It's a dream that火 would which we just iç przetizeander.
We have no hope that no matter what it does.
We can finally ump 관련 your way to talk.
A
I'll see you next time.
I'm telling you, man! I'm innocent, I swear!
Stop lying! Come on, I saw you steal it with my own friggin' eyes!
Are you completely sure it was him?
Yeah, no doubt about it.
I saw you with another woman! You were holding hands!
You gotta believe me, sweetheart! It wasn't me!
I'm sensing a theme. All these fights involve cases of mistaken identity.
You stupid twerk! What are you doing with that face?
What are you doing with that face?
Die!
Why don't you calm it down?
I hate you!
What are they so mad about?
Die anyway!
It's pretty unusual for Hika and Hina to fight.
Wait, what?
You don't actually think that's Hika, do you?
You don't actually think that's Hina, do you?
This is so weird.
This trip doesn't look anything like Hika! How dense can you guys be?
I was gonna say the same thing about you!
What the hell did you do with Hika? Give her back or I'll tell you what you want!
Where did you put Hina? Give her back or else!
Okay, I'm breaking this up.
Why don't we all play a nice game? You know, like Tag?
They're kind of starting to scare me.
You nasty little freak!
What'd you do that for, you stupid onion head?
How could you earn a kid?
I thought you were a good idiot!
Turns out he's a bad idiot!
Take a good look.
That's just a tiny old man who's dressed up like a girl.
Are your eyes stupid too, Arthur?
You're not just an idiot, you've lost your mind!
That girl's hot! Let's kill her dead!
Maybe you should hold off a minute.
Yeah, Bruce! Yeah! Get away!
Huh? A tiny old man?
That is so damn creepy!
Totally called it.
How is this possible?
Your face is my canvas.
You'll soon turn from a human into a work of art.
So, don't blink or you'll miss it.
Ah, beautiful.
So beautiful.
You're doing great.
I'm beautiful?
When I apply heat to your face, I can dilate your capillaries and lymph ducts.
I then make adjustments to the localized swelling and alter the shape of your face.
Very good!
Just stay still and relax.
Because you're about to become a beautiful work of art.
How do I look?
You're hideous.
You repulsive traitor!
A face that close could never bask in the light of soul!
What are you?
How dare you ask me that?
Fervor! Fervor!
Your blood is boiling now.
That's good.
Art is painful.
Art is a big bang!
Oh my!
It almost burns!
Yonah, don't waste our followers.
We only have so many.
Art, which means he wasn't...
We've finished our preparations.
The bugs are ready.
Now time to carry out our plan.
This town will be bathed in flame once more.
Art is true.
How are there this many misunderstandings happening at once?
Is there a shape-shifting fox in town?
Crazy.
They're going through the same thing I did.
No, not right now.
Between the confusion of the fires and the lies of our infiltrators, they'll have nothing to trust but soul.
Nothing else is worthy of their faith!
Asakusa's a place of power.
So perhaps the bugs we released will find a host.
Or give rise to a new demon.
We'll take advantage of the confusion and assault the ape.
Shall we begin?
It's an infernal!
Yonah just became an infernal too!
What do we do?
Should we put the infernals to rest?
Not now.
This is the seventh's jurisdiction.
There's nothing we can do until they give us permission.
We don't have a lot of time to burn, sir.
Tamaki's had training but hasn't taken vows as a nun yet.
So we can't put anyone to rest properly anyway.
Besides, most of these people don't want to be put to rest in the Imperial way.
If we have to die, there's no way we'd prefer to go out than at his hands.
The hands of Shinon Binemaru.
We need Wakka.
Where can he be right now?
We'll focus on helping civilians with the evacuation effort.
Yes, sir!
B-Baki!
Look out for a sniper!
Remember?
That shot?
Yeah.
Like before.
Get back, everyone!
I've got this!
I can't push it back!
Transmogrify!
You okay?
I'm fine, yeah.
It sure was cute how Spudder leapt into my arms, huh?
I'll draw their fire!
Be careful up there!
Stop!
You go with him.
Hurry.
And an enviable request.
The shot curved.
Even if they're curving their shots, this one clearly came from a different spot than the one before.
They're shooting on the run, using the smoke and chaos as cover.
If they attack again right away, they'll shoot from... over there!
Hey, what caused that explosion?
Just another arrow.
The blast was from my kick.
Deflection won't work here.
Those arrows are strong.
No outside force can change their trajectories.
What's more, that first shot came from way farther off than the two right before it.
Are they just doing this to try and keep their distance from me?
It's possible.
Or they could be trying to lure me away from my company.
But even if that's the case, I've got no choice.
Arthur!
You keep chasing them on foot!
I'll let you know where their shots come from!
Well, if you use tricky words like left or north, I'm not gonna know what you're saying.
So make sure you point, okay?
It's like he's proud of how dumb he is.
Let's go!
Where did you take the real Hikage?
You the one who turned into Company 8's captain?
Human beings just can't be trusted.
They lie and cheat.
Betray those they claim to love.
Or leave them by dying.
That's why we need souls so desperately.
I asked you two questions and neither one of them was about your sun god.
This is the last time I'll ask nicely.
You're hurting me!
Where did you take Hikage?
You're nothing but a godless, proto-nationalist scumbag!
I've nothing to say to someone like you!
A vial.
Did you?
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
Bring me the soul!
Do it!
The flame is the soul's breath.
The black smoke is the soul's release.
Ashes thou wert and art.
May thy soul...
Return to the great flame of fire.
Damn it how the hell did he do that it looks like infernals really can't be
made through artificial means sorry for not doing that in the local style no
worries that guy wasn't from Asakusa anyway by the way we tried to evacuate
the townspeople but they wouldn't listen to anything we said to them they need
to be led by someone they all trust
Walker
hey stop that's the wrong way they're part of town's burning down
Walker we got infernals over that way now too we can't stop them by ourselves anymore
okay I can go and see to the infernals you think you can get the townspeople out of
here no there have been imposters misleading them left and right
condo what would you do
where are you where'd you run
I've got you
it's no use you can't stop my arrow
I'm gonna go out on a limb here and say you must be members of the white clad
again the will of that sword's flame must be quite strong
let's do this
hey dumbass get out of the way
that's why you're swinging that thing
stay out of this will ya
why don't you stay out of it
since you can block my arrows I'll use ones that explode
get off you dumb devil
well I'm thinking you should just stay down there and say good night
the big guy's coming at us
we need to fight as a team like they do
oh we're finished
you don't have to tell me I get it
you never get anything I
I'm puts up with stuff that sucks man
teamwork is fine in theory
but we'll never be on the same page
let's try and split these two up
that does seem like the better plan
you've got longer reach
so you take the hooded guy
I can get in close with my speed
so I'll take the archer
Mr. Hoodie always moves to protect the archer
so we'll have to peel him away
let's go
the reason they're winning is because they don't get in each other's way
one stays back and the other keeps forward
we need to come up with a similar formation
I know
what now
this ought to work
gotcha
you won't get away from me
forfeit
I mean forbear
fall back
go
not this time
no
girl
go
come
if
you
go
I've got no clue who you were, but I'll end your suffering.
Way to hang in there, friend.
Come hear me.
笑えない日々を辿ったって 変わらない日々を呪ったって 決まった言葉が あなたを救えたいのだろう
届かないままの景色と 温まることない 痛みと肩を寄せ張って 歩いていた 遠いところへ行けるように
あなたの言う希望だとか 夢に乱りそうなら どんなに冷たくたって 愛してみせるよ
笑えない日々を辿ったって 変わらない日々を呪ったって 決まった言葉が あなたを救えたいのだろう
不甲斐ない声で叫んだって 熱をするに変わっていくこと
手が離れても また歩いていけるようにさよ
ただの言わずに そこからまた離るように
車椅子は?